(Amy:)Thank you for doing this.
(Bernadette:)Our pleasure.
(Bernadette:)You feeling okay?
(Amy:)We were together for so long,
(Amy:)I honestly don't know
what I'm feeling.
(Howard:)Well, that's
understandable.
(Howard:)You forgot.
It's called "happy."
(Amy:)Howard.
(Howard:)I'm not saying
anything bad.
(Howard:)Just that she was in love
with her captor
(Howard:)and somehow managed to escape
from his dark and crazy dungeon.
(Stuart:)I know
what you're going through.
My-my last breakup
was pretty tough.
(Amy:)Oh. What was her name?
(Stuart:)Hey, it's a true story.
(Stuart:)I don't need the third degree.
(gasps)
(Bernadette:)For God's sake, Sheldon,
what are you doing?
(Sheldon:)I didn't want
to come in.
(Sheldon:)I was told it would make
everyone feel uncomfortable.
(Sheldon:)So I'll just stay out here
(Sheldon:)and pretend that I don't
have to go to the bathroom.
(Bernadette:)Howard, do something.
(Howard:)I'm on it.